Guide to the Vassar College Dean of the College, Dean of the Faculty Records, 1917-1997 (bulk 1940-1996
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Claudia Goldin, ECON, Crego Lecture/Dinner, 28 Apr 1994 (Box 123)
- Computer Advisory Group (Box 123)
- Computer Literacy Program (Box 123)
- Committee on Computing, (5 folders) (Box 123)
- Lehman Grant, 1989-1990 (Box 123)
- Luce Women in Science Initiative (Box 123)
- Luce Foundation, 1988-1992; (3 folders) (Box 123)
- Nancy Dye / Mellon Foundation Appointment (Box 123)
- Hewlett Mellon Foundation, 1987-1992; (3 folders) (Box 124)
- Mellon Curricular Grant, 1989-1992; (3 folders) (Box 124)
- Mellon Faculty Development Fund, 1990-1991; (2 folders) (Box 124)
- Mellon Non-Western Studies Program, 1989-1992; (3 folders) (Box 124)
- Mellon Faculty Seminar (Box 124)
- Markey Scholars, 1990-1991 (Box 124)
- Grants - NEH (Box 124)
- NEH Proposals, 1991-1992 (Box 124)
- NEH, 1990-1992; (2 folders) (Box 124)
- NEH - Moses Nkondo (Box 124)
- NIH, 1990-1992; (2 folders) (Box 124)
- NSF, 1988-1991; (2 folders) (Box 124)
- Digital's Grants Strategy (Box 124)
- Ford Scholars' Program, 1989-1992; (4 folders) (Box 124)
- Ford Foundation, 1987-1992; (3 folders) (Box 124)
- Cameron Baird Grant (Box 124)
- Culpepper Foundation (Box 124)
- Dana Foundation, 1989-1991; (2 folders) (Box 124)
- Dupont Co. Grant (Box 124)
- Dreyfus Foundation (Box 124)
- Fulbright, 1990-1991 (Box 124)
- Grants - Miscellaneous (Box 124)
- Dana Library Initiative (Box 124)
- Gannett Foundation (Box 124)
- Gould Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 124)
- Grants - General, 1988 (Box 124)
- Grants Council, 1988-1991; (3 folders) (Box 124)
- Grants - Pending, 1989-1990 (Box 124)
- Grants, 1990-1992; (2 folders) (Box 124)
- HEGIS Reports (Box 124)
- Howard Hughes Grant, 1987-1992; (3 folders) (Box 125)
- GTE Grant (Box 125)
- Huber Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 125)
- IBM Grant, 1987-1991; (3 folders) (Box 125)
- Japan Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 125)
- Johnson Foundation (Box 125)
- Keck Foundation, 1989-1992; (3 folders) (Box 125)
- Kellogg Foundation, 1987-1991; (2 folders) (Box 125)
- Lehman Grant, 1990-1992; (2 folders) (Box 125)
- Institutional Review Board, 1968-1977, 1980; (2 folders) (Box 125)
- Language Fellows, 1988-1991; (3 folders) (Box 125)
- Library, 1987-1991; (5 folders) (Box 125)
- Northeastern Regional Dean's Meeting, 1987-1989; (3 folders) (Box 125)
- Personnel, 1988-1991; (3 folders) (Box 126)
- Registrar, 1988-1990; (2 folders) (Box 126)
- Safety, 1988-1991; (3 folders) (Box 126)
- URSI, 1988-1992; (5 folders) (Box 126)
- Career Development, 1988-1989; (2 folders) (Box 126)
- Committee on Computing, 1990-1991 (Box 126)
- Research Committee, (2 folders) (Box 126)
- Committee on Committees, 1988-1990 (Box 126)
- Linda Cool (Box 126)
- CCAS, 1989-1992; (5 folders) (Box 126)
- Day of Discussion, 20 Feb 1991 (Box 126)
- Dean of Studies, 1988-1991; (2 folders) (Box 126)
- Development, 1988-1992; (4 folders) (Box 126)
- Exploring Transfer, 1988-1991; (3 folders) (Box 127)
- Faculty Center, 1988-1992; (5 folders) (Box 127)
- Faculty Curriculum Retreat, 1988-1989; (3 folders) (Box 127)
- NSF, 1980-1983; (5 folders) (Box 127)
- Sloan Foundation, 1982-1991; (13 folders) (Box 127)
- URSI (Box 127)
- General Grants, 1984 (Box 127)
- Greenwood Grant, 1980 (Box 128)
- Starr Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 128)
- Topsfield, 1989-1990 (Box 128)
- Weight Watchers, 1989-1990 (Box 128)
- Grants, 1983 (Box 128)
- Grants - Miscellaneous, 1980-1987 (Box 128)
- Grants, 1980-1982 (Box 128)
- Mellon Foundation, 1983-1989; (13 folders) (Box 128)
- NEH Grants, 1980-1984; (3 folders) (Box 128)
- NSF Grants, 1983-1992; (6 folders) (Box 128)
- Grants, 1985 (Box 129)
- NIH, 1989-1991; (4 folders) (Box 129)
- NYNEX Grant, 1990-1991 (Box 129)
- Obesity Care Grant (Box 129)
- PEW Grant, 1987-1992; (7 folders) (Box 129)
- Research Corp. Grant (Box 129)
- Sherman Fairchild Foundation, 1989-1992; (3 folders) (Box 129)
- Sloan Foundation, 1989-1991; (2 folders) (Box 129)
- House Fellows, (8 folders) (Box 129)
- VC Observatory, 1994; (2 folders) (Box 130)
- CCP, 1992-1993 (Box 130)
- Sanders, 1992-1993 (Box 130)
- Collins / Nature Center, 1992-1994 (Box 130)
- Reports from Ken / Grants, 1994 (Box 130)
- Residential Life, 1993 (Box 130)
- Start-ups, 1992-1994; (2 folders) (Box 130)
- AVRC (Box 130)
- Freshman Orientation, 1993-1994 (Box 130)
- Sherman Fairchild Organization, 1992-1993 (Box 130)
- Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 130)
- Sloan / Oakes Ames (Box 130)
- Madrid, 1994 (Box 130)
- Annual Accreditation, 1993 (Box 130)
- Hughes, 1991-1993; (2 folders) (Box 130)
- Library / McAdams (Box 130)
- Admissions (Box 130)
- ARC (Box 130)
- Athletics, 1989-1990; (4 folders) (Box 130)
- URSI (Box 130)
- Enrollment, 1990; (2 folders) (Box 130)
- Senior Survey (Box 130)
- Student Data (Box 130)
- Faculty Retreat, 1990; (2 folders) (Box 130)
- Lock-up Committee (Box 131)
- Operating, 1990-1991 (Box 131)
- Enrollment (Box 131)
- Budgets, 1990-1993; (3 folders) (Box 132)
- Academic Space, (4 folders) (Box 132)
- New Physical Education Building (Box 132)
- New England Building (Box 132)
- Building Needs, 1985 (Box 132)
- Sherman Fairchild, 1989-1992 (Box 132)
- Miscellaneous Facilities (Box 132)
- Budgets, 1989-1990; (2 folders) (Box 132)
- Capital, [personnel], 1990-1992; (2 folders) (Box 132)
- Capital Campaign, (2 folders) (Box 132)
- Chemical Safety / Waste (Box 132)
- Academic Progress Support, 1990-1991 (Box 132)
- Academic Progress Support, 1989-1992; (2 folders) (Box 132)
- Education Information and Policy (Box 132)
- Financial Aid (Box 132)
- Research Committee Reserve (Box 132)
- Library Reserve (Box 132)
- General Department Review, 1988 (Box 132)
- Animal Care (Box 132)
- AVRC (Box 132)
- Energy Users Group (Box 132)
- Farm Subcommittee (Box 132)
- Athletics, (2 folders) (Box 132)
- Observatory Project (Box 132)
- Computer Science Review (Box 132)
- Grout Council, 1989 (Box 132)
- NYNEX (Box 132)
- Affirmative Action Committee (Box 132)
- FASC, 1977-1980; (12 folders) (Box 132)
- FCC/FPCC, 1977-1988; (10 folders) (Box 133)
- Files [Put] in[to] Storage [in] 1998: Appointment Books, 1989-1994; (12 volumes) (Box 133)
- Mail Logs, 1989-1994; (4 volumes (Box 133)
- Chronological Files, July 1992 - June 1995; (10 folders) (Box 134)
- Trustees, 1989 (Box 134)
- Grant Development Project, 1994-1995 (Box 134)
- CCP Subcommittee Report on the Evaluation of Teaching, 1990; (2 folders) (Box 134)
- Director of the Theatre (Box 134)
- Director of the Art Gallery (Box 134)
- Head Librarian Search Committee (Box 134)
- Athletic Director Search (Box 134)
- Capital Campaign, 1991-1992 (Box 134)
- Capital Campaign, 1991-1992 (Box 135)
- Comparison Profile - Class of 2000 (Box 135)
- Admission, 1991-1995; (4 folders) (Box 135)
- AAVC, 1991-1993; (3 folders) (Box 135)
- Academic Resource Center, 1991-1994; (3 folders) (Box 135)
- Academic Space, 1990 (Box 135)
- Academic Suffrage, 1993-1994 (Box 135)
- ACE/NIP (Box 135)
- ACDC (Box 135)
- Dean of Admission Search, 1994-1995 (Box 135)
- Admission - New Publications, 1993-1994 (Box 135)
- Admission - Tom Matos, 1992-1993; (2 folders) (Box 135)
- AAUP, 1991-1995; (5 folders) (Box 135)
- American Collegiate Conference, 1991-1996; (3 folders) (Box 135)
- American Council on Education, 1991-1993; (2 folders) (Box 135)
- Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area (Box 135)
- Berkshire Conference, 1992-1993; (2 folders) (Box 135)
- Board of Trustees - Academic Affairs Committee (Box 135)
- Budget Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 136)
- General, 1992-1993 (Box 136)
- Board Reports, 1988-1989, 1991-1992; (2 folders) (Box 136)
- Academic Affairs Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 136)
- Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 136)
- Development, 1992-1995; (3 folders) (Box 136)
- Atlanta Interest Event - N. Dye (Box 136)
- Capital Campaign Concept papers (Box 136)
- Capital Campaign Planning, 1992-1993; (3 folders) (Box 136)
- Trustees, 1989-1994; (5 folders) (Box 136)
- Trustees - Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 136)
- Career Development, 1990-1994; (4 folders) (Box 136)
- CCAS, 1992-1994; (2 folders) (Box 136)
- CCP (Box 137)
- CCP subcommittee report on the evaluation of teaching, 1990 (Box 137)
- CCP, 1992-1994; (3 folders) (Box 137)
- Chairs' Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 137)
- Committee on Computing (Box 137)
- Computing Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 137)
- FDF (Box 137)
- Faculty Meetings (Box 137)
- Exploring Transfer, 1991-1994; (3 folders) (Box 137)
- Facilities Operations, 1991-1994; (3 folders) (Box 137)
- FASC, 1985-1986, 1988-1989; (2 folders) (Box 137)
- Field Work, 1990-1995; (4 folders) (Box 137)
- Gaines Center for the Humanities, 1990-1993; (3 folders) (Box 137)
- Financial Aid, 1992-1995; (4 folders) (Box 138)
- FAO-COFHE FA Reports (Box 138)
- Financial Aid Office (Box 138)
- Computing Information System, 1994-1995 (Box 138)
- Academic Computing Center, 1991-1994; (3 folders) (Box 138)
- Allocations, 1992 (Box 138)
- Dean of Freshmen, 1989-1994; (7 folders) (Box 138)
- Dean of Studies, 1991-1995; (4 folders) (Box 138)
- Academic Program Support, 1991-1993; (2 folders) (Box 138)
- Ken Cool - Development (Box 138)
- MEDS (Box 138)
- H-7 Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 138)
- International Academy of Scholars, 1989-1993; (4 folders) (Box 138)
- Chuck Henry Library, 1992-1994; (2 folders) (Box 139)
- Library, 1991-1993; (2 folders) (Box 139)
- AVRC, 1988-1994; (8 folders) (Box 139)
- Northeast Regional Deans' Meeting, 1990-1995; (5 folders) (Box 139)
- Nursery School, 1988-1994; (8 folders) (Box 139)
- Part-time Faculty (Box 139)
- Personnel, 1991-1994; (3 folders) (Box 139)
- Language Fellows, 1991-1995; (4 folders) (Box 139)
- Project 30, 1988-1994; (4 folders) (Box 140)
- Roosevelt Library (Box 140)
- Retreat - Office (Box 140)
- Residential Life, 1988-1989 (Box 140)
- Residence (Box 140)
- Report of the Dean of the College to the Board of Trustees, 1983-1988 (Box 140)
- Safety Committee, 1991-1994; (4 folders) (Box 140)
- Eve Slater (Box 140)
- Society for Historians of American Foreign Relations (Box 140)
- SOS, 1992-1993 (Box 140)
- SOS - CONFIDENTIAL, 1 July 1988 - 31 Dec 1988; (2 folders) (Box 140)
- Staff Meeting, 1992-1994; (2 folders) (Box 140)
- Staffing Plans, 1993-1994 (Box 140)
- Student Evaluations (Box 140)
- Student/Faculty Ratio (Box 140)
- Student Fellows (Box 140)
- Student Life (Box 140)
- Student Right to Know and Campus Security Act (Box 140)
- Summer Program (Box 140)
- Summer Program, 1988-1992; (4 folders) (Box 140)
- Task Force on Instructional Needs - Resources (Box 140)
- Task Force - New Curriculum (Box 140)
- Teaching Evaluations, (2 folders) (Box 140)
- Triple A-VC (Box 140)
- URSI, 30 Sep 1992 - 1995; (5 folders) (Box 140)
- Students - Miscellaneous (Box 140)
- Text Encoding Initiative (Box 140)
- URSI Dinner, 12 Oct 1991 (Box 141)
- Priorities and Planning Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 141)
- Questionnaires, 1989-1994; (4 folders) (Box 141)
- Recruitment, 1988-1992; (4 folders) (Box 141)
- Registrar, 1991-1995; (5 folders) (Box 141)
- SAC, 1988-1990; (2 folders) (Box 141)
- Safety, 1994-1995 (Box 141)
- SOS (Box 141)
- Vassar Journals (Box 141)
- Vassar-Wesleyan-Colgate Program (Box 141)
- West Indies Lab College Associates (Box 141)
- WINKS (Box 141)
- Women and Science (Box 141)
- Women and Development, 1989-1990 (Box 141)
- Women's Health Initiative, 1989-1992; (3 folders) (Box 141)
- Registration Packet Notes Berkshire Conf (Box 141)
- Women in Science (Box 141)
- Berks - Budgeting Information (Box 141)
- Berks - Vassar Rooms Information, Reports (Box 141)
- Rentals (Box 141)
- Security (Box 141)
- Signs (Box 141)
- Service Request Notes - Buildings and Grounds (Box 141)
- Berks Notes (Box 141)
- Minutes from Meetings (Box 141)
- KB - Setups, Memos and Service Requests (Box 141)
- Berkshire Conference, 1993 (Box 141)
- Addenda - Program (Box 141)
- Berks - Room Assignments for Programs (Box 141)
- Berks - People that Owe [personnel] (Box 141)
- Berks - Receipts (Box 141)
- Tents (Box 141)
- To Do (Box 141)
- Berks - Printing Information (Box 142)
- Films (Box 142)
- Berks - General Correspondences (Box 142)
- Refund Letters (Box 142)
- ACDC - Meade Cerbino - Menu (Box 142)
- Linens (Box 142)
- Notes: Pending, To Do, ETC. over (Box 142)
- Receptions (Box 142)
- Book Exhibit (old) (Box 142)
- Berkshire Conference, (3 folders) (Box 142)
- Berks - Programs (old) (Box 142)
- Berks - Douglas/Rutgers Local Coordinator Report (Box 142)
- Berks - Douglas/Rutgers Program Report (Box 142)
- Tee Shirts [sic] (Box 142)
- Transportation (Box 142)
- Berks - Café/Retreat (Box 142)
- Berks - Vassar/Wellsley Reports (Box 142)
- Final Report, 1993 (Box 142)
- Berks - Student Handbook, 1993 (Box 142)
- Planning for Athletics (JK), 1953-1994; (3 folders) (Box 142)
- Planning for Blodget (JK), 1993-1995; (5 folders) (Box 142)
- Planning for new Library (JK), 1993-1995; (11 folders) (Box 143)
- Sanders Project, (4 folders) (Box 143)
- Department Files, 1991-1996; (20 folders) (Box 143)
- Department Files, 1991-1996; (91 folders) (Box 144)
- Department Files, 1991-1996; (87 folders) (Box 145)
- Enrollment Management, 1996-1997; (2 folders) (Box 145)
- CCP, 1995-1997; (3 folders) (Box 146)
- Evelyn Clark Fund, 1990-1995; (5 folders) (Box 146)
- Garnsey Fund, 1987-1997; (10 folders) (Box 146)
- Novy Fund, 1987-1995; (6 folders) (Box 146)
- Randolph Fund, 1990-1995; (6 folders) (Box 146)
- Sitomer Fund, 1991-1994; (3 folders) (Box 146)
- Matthew Vassar [Lecture Fund], 1987-1996; (10 folders) (Box 146)
- Nursery School, 1992-1993 (Box 147)
- Facilities Planning, 1992-1993 (Box 147)
- Teaching Evaluation Revisions, 1994 (Box 147)
- Candidate Responses Re: Alumnae Reports (Box 147)
- CEQ/Teaching Consultants (Box 147)
- Retreat/CEQs, 1993 (Box 147)
- CCP Subcommittee - Evaluation of Teaching (Box 147)
- Science Task Force, 1990 (Box 147)
- Multi-Cultural Task Force (Box 147)
- Budget Analyses (Box 147)
- HHMI Proposal, 1995 (Box 147)
- Peterson's Sciences Guide (Box 147)
- Computing Requests, 1995-1996 (Box 147)
- Chronological File (Box 147)
- Committee on Committees, 1989-1990 (Box 147)
- Information (Box 147)
- Appointed and Elected Faculty Committees, 1987-1988 (Box 147)
- Majors Entertainment, (3 folders) (Box 147)
- Old Files (Box 147)
- ICFC (Box 147)
- Kendrick House, 1985-1988; (3 folders) (Box 147)
- Fisher Case Files (Box 148)
- Fisher Case Files (Box 149)
- Fisher Case Files (Box 150)
- Fisher Case Files (Box 151)
- Fisher Case Files (Box 152)
- Fisher Case Files (Box 153)